A Guide to the Correspondence and subject files of the Director of the Virginia Housing Development Authority, 1972-2012
Library of Virginia
- Correspondence, subject files, and board meeting records (Accessions 44847, 45144, 45238, 45268, 51901 51962), 1972-2010., Extent: 37 cu. ft. (37 boxes).
  - Federal Home Loan Bank Advisory Council: Charity housing trends (Acc. 45144), 1991-1992 (Box 4)
  - Federal Home Loan Bank Advisory Council: Community Enterprise (Acc. 45268), 1994 (Box 3)
  - Federal Home Loan Bank Advisory Council: Correspondence (Acc. 45144), 1992 January-December (Box 4)
  - Federal Home Loan Bank Advisory Council: Correspondence (Acc. 45268), 1994 January-June (Box 3)
  - Federal Home Loan Bank Advisory Council: Correspondence (Acc. 45268), 1994 July-December (Box 3)
  - Federal Home Loan Bank Advisory Council: General (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 5)
  - Federal Home Loan Bank Advisory Council: Meeting (Acc. 44847), 1990 May (Box 5)
  - Federal Home Loan Bank Advisory Council: Meeting (Acc. 44847), 1991 September (Box 5)
  - Federal Home Loan Bank Advisory Council: Meetings (Acc. 44847), 1990-1991 (Box 5)
  - Federal Home Loan Bank Advisory Council: Meeting (Acc. 45268), 1994 June (Box 3)
  - Federal Home Loan Bank of Atlanta Advisory Council: Meetings (Acc. 45144), 1991 (Box 4)
  - Federal Housing Finance Board (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 4)
  - Federal Housing Finance Board (Acc. 45268), 1994 January-June (Box 3)
  - Federal Housing Finance Board (Acc. 45268), 1994 July-December (Box 3)
  - Finance Division: Bear Stearns Municipal Market Update (Acc. 45268), 1994 (Box 3)
  - Finance Division: BMIR Loans (Acc. 45238), 1988 (Box 5)
  - Finance Division: BMIR Loans (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 5)
  - Finance Division: BMIR Loans (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 6)
  - Finance Division: BMIR Loans (Acc. 45268), 1994 (Box 3)
  - Finance Division: Bond Refunding (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 5)
  - Finance Division: Director's correspondence (Acc. 44847), 1991 January-June (Box 6)
  - Finance Division: Director's correspondence (Acc. 45144), 1991 July-1992 June (Box 5)
  - Finance Division: Dircetor's Correspondence (Acc. 45238), 1992 July-December (Box 5)
  - Finance Division: Director's Correspondence (Acc. 45238), 1993 January-June (Box 5)
  - Finance Division: Director's correspondence (Acc. 45268), 1993 July-December (Box 3)
  - Finance Division: Director's correspondence (Acc. 45268), 1994 January-June (Box 3)
  - Finance Division: Director's correspondence (Acc. 51962), 2010 Jan-June (Box 3)
  - Finance Division: Director's correspondence (Acc. 51962), 2010 July-Dec (Box 3)
  - Finance Division: Merrell Lynch report (Acc. 45238), 1992 (Box 5)
  - Finance Division: Moody's Rating Letters (Acc. 44847), 1988-1989 (Box 6)
  - Finance Division: Moody's Rating Letters (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 6)
  - Finance Division: Moody's Rating Letters (Acc. 45144), 1991 (Box 5)
  - Finance Division: Multifamily Bond Refunding (Acc. 45238), 1992 (Box 5)
  - Finance Division: S and P Rating Letters (Acc. 44847), 1987-1990 (Box 6)
  - Finance, Secretary of: Bonded Indebtedness (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 9)
  - Finance, Secretary of: Correspondence (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 2)
  - Finance, Secretary of: Correspondence (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 9)
  - Finance, Secretary of: Correspondence (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 2)
  - Finance, Secretary of: Correspondence (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 7)
  - Finanance, Secretary of: Correspondence (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 6)
  - Finance, Secretary of: State Treasurer (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 9)
  - Finance, Secretary of: State Treasurer (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 5)
  - Finance, Secretary of: Correspondence (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 8)
  - Financing programs (Acc. 45238), n.d. (Box 2)
  - General Assembly: Correspondence (Acc. 44847), 1989 (Box 2)
  - General Assembly: Correspondence (Acc. 45238), 1991 July-December (Box 8)
  - General Assembly: HB 754 (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 2)
  - General Assembly: Legislative changes (Acc. 45144), 1991 (Box 7)
  - General Assembly: Senate Finance Committee (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 7)
  - General Assembly: Status of legislation memos (Acc. 44847), 1989 (Box 2)
  - General Assembly: Status of legislation memos (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 9)
  - General Auditor (Acc. 51901), 2009 (Box 1)
  - General correspondence (Acc. 44847), 1990 July-1991 August (Box 7)
  - Ginnie Mae (Acc. 51901), 2009 Apr-June (Box 1)
  - Governor, Office of the: Correspondence (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 2)
  - Governor, Office of the: Correspondence (Acc. 44847), 1991 January-June (Box 9)
  - Governor, Office of the: Correspondence (Acc. 44847), 1991 July-December (Box 9)
  - Governor, Office of the: Correspondence (Acc. 45144), 1992 January-June (Box 7)
  - Governor, Office of the: Correspondence (Acc. 45238), 1992 July-December (Box 8)
  - Governor, Office of the: Correspondence (Acc. 45238), 1993 January-June (Box 8)
  - Governor, Office of the: Washington Liaison Office (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 2)
  - Governor, Office of the: Washington Liaison Office (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 9)
  - Governor, Office of the: Washington Liaison Office (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 7)
  - Governor, Office of the: Washington Liaison Office (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 8)
  - Halifax County Housing Study Commission (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 4)
  - Health and Human Resources, Secretary of: Board for Rights of the Disabled (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 2)
  - Health and Human Resources, Secretary of: Coalition for Mentally Disabled Citizens of Virginia (Acc. 44847), 1990-1991 (Box 9)
  - Health and Human Resources, Secretary of: Coalition for Mentally Disabled Citizens of Virginia (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 7)
  - Health and Human Resources, Secretary of: Correspondence (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 2)
  - Health and Human Resources, Secretary of: Correspondence (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 9)
  - Health and Human Resources, Secretary of: Correspondence (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 7)
  - Health and Human Resources, Secretary of: DMHRSAS/VHDA Congregate Home (Acc. 44847), 1988-1990 (Box 2)
  - Health and Human Resources, Secretary of: DMHRSAS/VHDA Congregate Home (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 9)
  - Health and Human Resources, Secretary of: DMHRSAS/VHDA Congregate Home (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 9)
  - Health and Human Resources, Secretary of: DMHRSAS/VHDA/DHCD Joint Program (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 9)
  - Health and Human Resources, Secretary of: DMHRSAS/VHDA/DHCD Joint Program (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 9)
  - Health and Human Resources, Secretary of: Migrant Worker Committee (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 2)
  - Health and Human Resources, Secretary of: Migrant Worker Committee (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 9)
  - Health and Human Resources, Secretary of: SAVE Task Force (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 2)
  - Housing and Community Development, Dept. of: CHAS (Acc. 45238), 1993 January-June (Box 7)
  - Housing and Community Development, Dept. of: CORD (Acc. 45238), 1992-1993 (Box 7)
  - Housing and Community Development, Dept. of: Correspondence (Acc. 45238), 1992 July-December (Box 7)
  - Housing and Community Development, Dept. of: Correspondence (Acc. 45238), 1993 January-June (Box 7)
  - Housing and Community Development, Dept. of: Correspondence (Acc. 51901), 2009 Oct-Dec (Box 2)
  - Housing and Community Development, Dept. of: Governor's Housing Conference (Acc. 45238), 1992 (Box 7)
  - Housing and Community Development, Dept. of: Housing News (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 8)
  - Housing and Community Development, Dept. of: Housing Outreach Fund state report (Acc. 45144), 1991-1992 (Box 7)
  - Housing and Community Development, Dept. of: Housing Partnership Fund (Acc. 44847), 1989 (Box 2)
  - Housing and Community Development, Dept. of: Housing Partnership Fund (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 9)
  - Housing and Community Development, Dept. of: Housing Partnership Fund (Acc. 44847), 1991 January-June (Box 9)
  - Housing and Community Development, Dept. of: Housing Partnership Fund (Acc. 44847), 1991 July-1992 June (Box 9)
  - Housing and Community Development, Dept. of: Housing Partnership Fund (Acc. 45238), 1992 July-December (Box 8)
  - Housing and Community Development, Dept. of: Housing Partnership Fund (Acc. 45238), 1993 January-June (Box 8)
  - Housing and Community Development, Dept. of: Housing Partnership Fund - Admission Fee (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 8)
  - Housing and Community Development, Dept. of: Housing Partnership Fund - Memo of understanding (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 9)
  - Housing and Community Development, Dept. of: Housing Partnership Fund status reports (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 9)
  - Housing and Community Development, Dept. of: Low income housing tax credits (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 7)
  - Housing Management Division: Developments under discussion (Acc. 44847), 1988-1989 (Box 1)
  - Housing Management Division: Director's correspondence (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 1)
  - Housing Management Division: Director's correspondence (Acc. 44847), 1991 January-June (Box 6)
  - Housing Management Division: Director's correspondence (Acc. 45155), 1991 July-1992 June (Box 5)
  - Housing Management Division: Director's correspondenc (Acc. 45238), 1992 July-December (Box 5)
  - Housing Management Division: Director's correspondence (Acc. 45238), 1993 January-June (Box 5)
  - Housing Management Division: Director's correspondence (Acc. 45268), 1993 July-December (Box 3)
  - Housing Management Division: Director's correspondence (Acc. 45268), 1994 January-June (Box 3)
  - Housing Management Division: Matching Program (Acc. 44847), 1989-1990 (Box 1)
  - Housing Management Division: Matching Program (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 6)
  - Housing Management Division: Moderate Rehabilitation (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 1)
  - Housing Management Division: New Construction (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 1)
  - Housing Management Division: New Construction (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 6)
  - Housing Management Division: New Construction (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 5)
  - Housing Management Division: New Construction (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 5)
  - Housing Management Division: New Construction (Acc. 45268), 1994 (Box 3)
  - Housing Management: Robert Wood Johnson (Acc. 44847), 1988-1990 (Box 1)
  - Housing Management Division: Robert Wood Johnson (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 6)
  - Housing Management Division: Robert Wood Johnson (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 5)
  - Housing Management Division: Robert Wood Johnson (Acc. 45268), 1994 (Box 3)
  - Housing Management Division: Section 8 Existing (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 1)
  - Housing Management Division: Section 8 Existing (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 6)
  - Housing Management Division: Section 8 Existing (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 5)
  - Housing Management Division: Section 8 Existing (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 5)
  - Housing Management Division: Section 8 Existing (Acc. 45268), 1994 (Box 3)
  - Housing Management Division: Vouchers (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 1)
  - Housing Study Commission (Acc. 44847), 1989 (Box 2)
  - Housing Study Commission (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 6)
  - Housing Study Commission (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 6)
  - Housing Study Commission (Acc. 45238), 1992 (Box 8)
  - Housing Study Commission - Annualy Workshop (Acc. 43861), 1979 Oct (Box 3)
  - Housing Study Commission: Public Hearing (Acc. 45238), 1992 (Box 8)
  - Housing Study Commission: Retreat work session (Acc. 44847), 1989 (Box 2)
  - Housing Study Commission: Retreat work session (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 9)
  - HUD Central Office (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 2)
  - HUD Central Office (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 9)
  - HUD Central Office (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 7)
  - HUD Central Office (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 8)
  - HUD Central Office: ACC payments dispute (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 2)
  - HUD Central Office: FHA (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 8)
  - HUD Central (Acc. 51962), 2010 (Box 1)
  - HUD DC Area Office (Acc. 43861), 1977-1979 (Box 5)
  - HUD DC Area Office(Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 2)
  - HUD DC Area Office (Acc. 44847) 1991 (Box 9)
  - HUD DC Area Office (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 7)
  - HUD DC Area Office (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 8)
  - HUD DC Area Office (Acc. 51901), 2009 (Box 2)
  - HUD Flexible Subsidy Meeting (Acc. 43861), 1980 Feb (Box 5)
  - HUD General (Acc. 43861), 1980-1981 (Box 5)
  - HUD Interagency Group (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 1)
  - HUD Interagency Group (Acc. 45238), 1991 (Box 8)
  - HUD Interagency Group (Acc. 51901), 2009 (Box 2)
  - HUD Neighborhood Strategy Area Program (Acc. 43861), 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  - HUD Region II Philadelphia Office (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 1)
  - HUD Region III Philadelphia Office (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 7)
  - HUD Region III Philadelphia Office (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 8)
  - HUD Regional Reforms for Affordable Housing (Acc. 45238), 1992-1993 (Box 8)
  - HUD Richmond Office (Acc. 43861), 1978-1981 (Box 5)
  - HUD Richmond Office (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 1)
  - HUD Richmond Office (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 9)
  - HUD Richmond Office - Program Description (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 9)
  - HUD Richmond Area Office (Acc. 45144), 1992 January-August (Box 7)
  - HUD Richmond Office (Acc. 45238), 1992 September-December (Box 8)
  - HUD Richmond Office (Acc. 45238), 1993 January-April (Box 8)
  - HUD Richmond Office (Acc. 45238), 1993 May-August (Box 8)
  - HUD Section 8 (Acc. 43861), 1979-1981 (Box 5)
  - HUD Section 8 - Set aside allocation funds (Acc. 43861), 1980-1981 (Box 5)
  - HUD Title 1 (Acc. 43861), 1978 (Box 5)
  - Human Resources (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 8)
  - Internal Auditor (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 5)
  - Internal Auditor (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 3)
  - Internal Auditor (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 4)
  - Internal Auditor (Acc. 51901), 2009 (Box 1)
  - Internal Auditor - Audit and Management (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 3)
  - Internal Auditor - Audit follow-up (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 4)
  - Internal Auditor - Peat Marwick (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 3)
  - Internal Audit Director (Acc. 45268), 1994 (Box 3)
  - ITS: Business Systems (Acc. 51962), 2010 (Box 3)
  - Leadership Team (Acc. 51962), 2010 Jan-Mar (Box 1)
  - Leadership Team (Acc. 51962), 2010Apr-June (Box 1)
  - Leadership Team (Acc. 51962), 2010 July-Sept (Box 1)
  - Leadership Team (Acc. 51962), 2010 Oct-Dec (Box 1)
  - Legal Division: Arbitrage regulations (Acc. 45268), 1994 (Box 4)
  - Legal Division: Bond counsel (Acc. 45268), 1993 (Box 4)
  - Legal Division: Christian Barton (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 6)
  - Legal Division: Christian Barton (Acc. 45238), 1999 (Box 5)
  - Legal Division: General Counsel correspondence (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 1)
  - Legal Division: General Counsel correspondence (Acc. 45144), 1991 July-1992 June (Box 5)
  - Legal Division: General Counsel correspondence (Acc. 45238), 1992 July-December (Box 5)
  - Legal Division: General Counsel correspondence (Acc. 45238), 1993 January-June (Box 5)
  - Legal Division: General Counsel correspondence (Acc. 45268), 1993 July-December (Box 4)
  - Legal Division: General Counsel correspondence (Acc. 45268), 1994 January-June (Box 4)
  - Legal Division: General Counsel correspondence (Acc. 44847), 1991 January-June (Box 6)
  - Legal Division: General Counsel correspondence (Acc. 51901), 2009 Jan-June (Box 1)
  - Legal Division: General Counsel correspondence (Acc. 51901), 2009 July-Dec (Box 1)
  - Legal Division: General Counsel correspondence (Acc. 51962), 2010 Jan-June (Box 1)
  - Legal Division: General Counsel correspondence (Acc. 51962), 2010 July-Dec (Box 1)
  - Legal Division: Procurement Procedures (Acc. 45238), 1990 (Box 5)
  - Legal Division: Public hearing (Acc. 45268), 1994 June (Box 4)
  - Legal Division: Single Family R and R changes (Acc. 45268), 1994 January-March (Box 4)
  - Legal Division: Single Family R and R changes (Acc. 45268), 1994 April-June (Box 4)
  - Legal Division: Single Family R and R changes - Letters from public (Acc. 45268), 1994 March (Box 4)
  - Legal Division: Single Family R and R changes - Letters from public (Acc. 45268), 1994 April (Box 4)
  - Legal Division: Single Family R and R changes - Letters from public (Acc. 45268), 1994 May (Box 4)
  - Legal Division: Single Family R and R changes - Letters from public (Acc. 45268), 1994 June (Box 4)
  - Legal Division: Single Family R and R changes - Letters from public (Acc. 45268), 1994 July (Box 4)
  - Legal Division: Single Family R and R changes - News articles (Acc. 45268), 1994 (Box 4)
  - Legislative Services, Div. of: Correspondence (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 2)
  - Legislative Services, Div. of: Correspondence (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 9)
  - Legislative Service, Div. of: Correspondence (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 7)
  - Legislators: State (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 4)
  - Legislators: State (Acc. 44847), 1991 January-June (Box 4)
  - Legislators: State (Acc. 45144), 1991 July-December (Box 3)
  - Legislators: State (Acc. 45144), 1992 January-June (Box 3)
  - Legislators: State (Acc. 45238), 1992 July-December (Box 4)
  - Legislators: State (Acc. 45238), 1993 January-June (Box 4)
  - Legislators: State (Acc. 45268), 1993 July-December (Box 2)
  - Legislators: State (Acc. 45268), 1994 January-June (Box 2)
  - Legislators: State (Acc. 51901), 2009 Jan-June (Box 1)
  - Legislators: State (Acc. 51901), 2009 July-Dec (Box 1)
  - Legislators: State (Acc. 51962), 2010 Jan-June (Box 1)
  - Legislators: State (Acc. 51962), 2010 July-Dec (Box 1)
  - Legislators: State - Meeting with Sen. Colgan (Acc. 45268), 1993 (Box 2)
  - Legislators: State - Meeting with Del. DeBoer (Acc. 45268), 1993 (Box 2)
  - Legislators: State - Meeting with Del. Diamonsteon (Acc. 45268), 1993 (Box 2)
  - Legislators: State - Meeting with Sen. Mayre (Acc. 45268), 1993 (Box 2)
  - Legislators: United States (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 4)
  - Legislators: United States (Acc. 44847), 1991 January-June (Box 4)
  - Legislators: United States (Acc. 45144), 1991 July-December (Box 3)
  - Legislators: United States (Acc. 45144), 1992 January-June (Box 3)
  - Legislators: United States (Acc. 45238), 1992 July-December (Box 4)
  - Legislators: United States (Acc. 45238), 1993 January-June (Box 4)
  - Legislators: United States (Acc. 45268), 1993 July-December (Box 2)
  - Legislators: United States (Acc. 45268), 1994 January-June (Box 2)
  - Legislators: United States (Acc. 51901), 2009 Jan-June (Box 1)
  - Legislators: United States (Acc. 51901), 2009 July-Dec (Box 1)
  - Legislators: United States (Acc. 51962), 2010 Jan-June (Box 1)
  - Legislators: United States (Acc. 51962), 2010 July-Dec (Box 1)
  - Minority Outreach Loan Programs Seminar (Acc. 45144), 1991 Dec (Box 3)
  - Miscellaneous meetings and speaking engagements (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 3)
  - Miscellaneous: Federal Government (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous: United Way and Southern Growth Policies Board (Acc. 45144), undated (Box 3)
  - Low Income Housing Tax Credit (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 8)
  - Mental Health, Dept. of (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 8)
  - Miscellaneous: Local Government (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 9)
  - Miscellaneous: State Agencies (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 2)
  - Mortgage Roundtable meeting (Acc. 45238), 1993 November (Box 5)
  - Multifamily Division: Asset Management (Acc. 51962), 2010 Jan-June (Box 1)
  - Multifamily Division: Asset Management (Acc. 51962), 2010 July-Dec (Box 1)
  - Multifamily Division: Development (Acc. 51901), 2009 Jan-June (Box 1)
  - Multifamily Division: Development (Acc. 51962), 2010 Jan-June (Box 1)
  - Multifamily Division: Development (Acc. 51962), 2009 July-Dec (Box 1)
  - Multifamily Division: Director's correspondence (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 1)
  - Multifamily Division: Director's correspondence (Acc. 44847), 1991 January-June (Box 6)
  - Multifamily Division: Director's correspondence (Acc. 45144), 1991 July-1992 June (Box 5)
  - Multifamily Division: Director's correspondence (Acc. 45238), 1992 July-December (Box 6)
  - Multifamily Divsion: Director's correspondence (Acc. 45238), 1993 January-June (Box 6)
  - Multifamily Division: Director's correspondence (Acc. 45268), 1993 July-December (Box 4)
  - Multifamily Division: Director's correspondence (Acc. 45268), 1994 January-June (Box 4)
  - Multifamily Division: Low Income Housing Tax Credit (LIHTC) (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 1)
  - Multifamily Division: Low Income Housing Tax Credit (LIHTC) (Acc. 44847), 1990 September-December (Box 6)
  - Multifamily Division: Low Income Housing Tax Credit (LIHTC) (Acc. 44847), 1991 January-June (Box 6)
  - Multifamily Division: Low Income Housing Tax Credit (LIHTC) (Acc. 44847), 1991 July-December (Box 6)
  - Multifamily Division: Low Income Housing Tax Credit (LIHTC) (Acc. 51901), 2009 Jan-June (Box 1)
  - Multifamily Division: Low Income Housing Tax Credit (LIHTC) (Acc. 51901), 2009 July-Dec (Box 1)
  - Multifamily Division: Low Income Housing Tax Credit (LIHTC) (Acc. 51962), 2010 Jan-June (Box 1)
  - Multifamily Division: Low Income Housing Tax Credit (LIHTC) (Acc. 51962), 2010 July-Dec (Box 1)
  - Multifamily Division: Mortgage Loan Committee (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 1)
  - Multifamily Division: Mortgage Loan Committee (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 1)
  - Multifamily Division: Mortgage Loan Committee (Acc. 45144), 1992 January-June (Box 5)
  - Multifamily Division: Mortgage Loan Committee (Acc. 45238), 1992 July-December (Box 6)
  - Multifamily Division: Mortgage Loan Committee (Acc. 45238), 1993 January-June (Box 6)
  - Multifamily Division: Mortgage Loan Committee (Acc. 45268), 1993 July-December (Box 4)
  - Multifamily Division: Mortgage Loan Committee (Acc. 45268), 1994 January-April (Box 4)
  - Multifamily Division: Mortgage Loan Committee (Acc. 45268), 1994 May-August (Box 4)
  - Multifamily Division: Mortgage Loan Committee (Acc. 45268), 1994 September-December (Box 4)
  - Multifamily Division: Production Updage Reports (Acc. 45238), 1992-1993 (Box 6)
  - Multifamily Division: Production Update Reports (Acc. 45268), 1994 (Box 4)
  - National Association of Home Builders Mortgage Roundtable (Acc. 45144), 1992 June-December (Box 4)
  - National Association of Home Builders Mortgage Roundtable (Acc. 45238), 1993 July-December (Box 5)
  - National Association of Home Builders Mortgage Roundtable (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 6)
  - National Association of Home Builders Mortgage Roundtable (Acc. 45268), 1994 Janurary-June (Box 3)
  - Nations Bank (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 3)
  - Natural Resources, Secretary of: Correspondence (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 2)
  - Natural Resources, Secretary of: Correspondence (Acc. 44847) 1991 (Box 9)
  - Natural Resources, Secretary of: Correspondence (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 7)
  - Natural Resources, Secretary of: Correspondence (Acc. 51901), 2009 (Box 2)
  - Nonprofit Housing Groups (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 6)
  - Nonprofit Housing Groups (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 4)
  - Nonprofit Housing Groups (Acc. 45238), 1992 (Box 5)
  - Nonprofit Housing Groups (Acc. 45268), 1993 (Box 5)
  - Nonprofit Housing Groups (Acc. 51901), 2009 (Box 1)
  - Nonprofit Housing Groups (Acc. 51962), 2010 (Box 1)
  - Peat Marwick (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 5)
  - Planning and Research Division: Director's Correspondence (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 1)
  - Planning and Research Division: Director's Correspondence (Acc. 44847), 1991 January-June (Box 7)
  - Planning and Research Division: Director's Correspondence (Acc. 45144), 1991 July-1992 June (Box 5)
  - Planning and Research Division: Director's correspondence (Acc. 45238), 1992 July-December (Box 6)
  - Planning and Research Division: Director's correspondence (Acc. 45238), 1993 January-June (Box 6)
  - Planning and Research Division: Director's correspondence (Acc. 45268), 1993 July-December (Box 5)
  - Planning and Research Division: Director's correspondence (Acc. 45268), 1994 January-July (Box 5)
  - Planning and Research Division: HECM Loan Program (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 5)
  - Planning and Research Division: HECM Loan Program (Acc. 45268), 1994 (Box 5)
  - Planning and Research Division: Preservation (Acc. 45238), 1991-1993 (Box 6)
  - Planning and Research Division: Regional Loan Fund Demonstration (Acc. 45268), 1994 (Box 5)